#### Contact

2009pranalipa@gmail.com LinkedIn Profile

### Top Skills · See all

Pharmacology ·
Pharmacovigilance · Medical
Writing · Clinical Research ·
Clinical Data Management ·

Drug Discovery · Drug Safety · Biotechnology · Pre-clinical Studies · Animal Behaviour

#### Accomplishments · See all

4 Publications · 3 Languages · 2 Certifications · 1 Honor & Award

# Pranali Paradkar

Executive - Regulatory Affairs (Pharmacovigilance role) at Flamingo Pharmaceuticals Ltd

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

### Summary

Have experience in Pharmacovigilance and Regulatory Affairs (RIMS) fields. Highly motivated with strong business acumen, work ethics, and desire to achieve professional growth and advancement through relevant experience, learning from others, reading, and attending trainings. Demonstrated excellent communication, interpersonal, and organizational skills; able to prioriti...

Read more

### Experience

## Executive - Regulatory Affairs (Pharmacovigilance

role) · Flamingo Pharmaceuticals Ltd

April 2019 - Present · Mumbai Area, India

• To perform all Pharmacovigilence related activities.• Preparation of PSUR, PADER.• Preparation of RMP.• Preparation of SmPC and PIL.• Responsible for monitoring of the compliance of all outsourced Pharmacovigilance activities.• Responsible for preparation of Pharmacovigilance SOPs.• Handling of safety rela

## $\textbf{Regulatory Affairs Associate} \cdot \textbf{Teva Pharmaceuticals}$

July 2017 - March 2018 (9 months) · Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

## Drug Safety Associate - Pharmacovigilance · Cognizant

September 2015 - June 2017 (1 year 10 months) · Mumbai Area, India

#### Pharmaceutical Internship · Sandoz India Pvt Ltd

June 2011 - June 2011 (1 month) · Navi Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

#### Education

Dr. L.H.Hiranandani College of Pharmacy, University of Mumbai

Master's Degree, Pharmacology (2013 - 2015)